Contact

4054738383 (Home) antonio_watson08@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/antoniowatson-668610a1 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing

BLS

ACL<u>S</u>

Certifications

Basic Life Support (BLS)

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Registered Nurse

Antonio Watson

Registered Nurse

Plano, Texas

Summary

Experienced Travel Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the staffing and recruiting industry. Skilled in Nursing Education, Medical-Surgical, Pediatrics, Medication Administration, and Patient Education. Strong healthcare services professional with a Associate's in applied Science focused in Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse from Oklahoma City Community College.

Experience

Reward staffing
Registered Nurse
June 2019 - Present (1 year 1 month)
Dallas/Fort Worth Area

UT Southwestern Medical Center Registered Nurse October 2018 - April 2019 (7 months)

Supplemental Health Care
Travel Nurse
December 2015 - November 2018 (3 years)
Dallas/Fort Worth Area

SSM Health Care Registered Nurse March 2010 - March 2016 (6 years 1 month)

St. Anthony's Hospital
3 years 3 months

LPN
February 2012 - May 2013 (1 year 4 months)

CNA March 2010 - February 2012 (2 years)

Education

Oklahoma City Community College
Associate's in applied Science, Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2010 - 2014)